import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const katakanaForeignSounds: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"wi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ジェ",
      "ファ",
      "ウィ",
      "ウォ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ウィ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ウィ\"?",
    "options": [
      "wi",
      "ti",
      "tso",
      "je"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"we\"?",
    "options": [
      "チェ",
      "ツェ",
      "ファ",
      "ウェ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ウェ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ウェ\"?",
    "options": [
      "we",
      "fyu",
      "fi",
      "tso"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "we"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"wo\"?",
    "options": [
      "チェ",
      "ツェ",
      "ウォ",
      "ツァ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ウォ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ウォ\"?",
    "options": [
      "fe",
      "wo",
      "che",
      "tso"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "wo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"ti\"?",
    "options": [
      "ツェ",
      "チェ",
      "ウォ",
      "ティ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ティ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ティ\"?",
    "options": [
      "fyu",
      "ti",
      "tsi",
      "wi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ti"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"di\"?",
    "options": [
      "ツェ",
      "フュ",
      "ディ",
      "チェ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ディ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ディ\"?",
    "options": [
      "che",
      "di",
      "vu",
      "ti"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "di"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"che\"?",
    "options": [
      "チェ",
      "ウェ",
      "ツォ",
      "ジェ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "チェ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"チェ\"?",
    "options": [
      "tsi",
      "che",
      "fa",
      "tso"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "che"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"je\"?",
    "options": [
      "ディ",
      "ジェ",
      "シェ",
      "ツィ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ジェ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ジェ\"?",
    "options": [
      "fe",
      "je",
      "fa",
      "fo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "je"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"she\"?",
    "options": [
      "ツィ",
      "ジェ",
      "シェ",
      "ティ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "シェ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"シェ\"?",
    "options": [
      "she",
      "fi",
      "fe",
      "che"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "she"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"tsa\"?",
    "options": [
      "ツァ",
      "ファ",
      "フォ",
      "ウェ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ツァ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ツァ\"?",
    "options": [
      "fi",
      "tsa",
      "fo",
      "ti"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tsa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"tsi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ウェ",
      "ツィ",
      "ディ",
      "チェ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ツィ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ツィ\"?",
    "options": [
      "tsi",
      "wo",
      "fi",
      "ti"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tsi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"tse\"?",
    "options": [
      "フュ",
      "ツェ",
      "ヴ",
      "ツァ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ツェ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ツェ\"?",
    "options": [
      "che",
      "je",
      "tso",
      "tse"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tse"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"tso\"?",
    "options": [
      "ウィ",
      "ディ",
      "ツォ",
      "ウェ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ツォ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ツォ\"?",
    "options": [
      "tso",
      "je",
      "fe",
      "fyu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "tso"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"vu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ヴ",
      "ファ",
      "ウォ",
      "ツィ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ヴ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ヴ\"?",
    "options": [
      "fo",
      "je",
      "tse",
      "vu"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "vu"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"fa\"?",
    "options": [
      "ウィ",
      "ファ",
      "ツェ",
      "フォ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ファ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"ファ\"?",
    "options": [
      "wi",
      "we",
      "je",
      "fa"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "fa"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"fi\"?",
    "options": [
      "ウェ",
      "フィ",
      "ウィ",
      "ティ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "フィ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"フィ\"?",
    "options": [
      "che",
      "fi",
      "ti",
      "tsi"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "fi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"fe\"?",
    "options": [
      "ティ",
      "フェ",
      "ヴ",
      "ツォ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "フェ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"フェ\"?",
    "options": [
      "wo",
      "fyu",
      "wi",
      "fe"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "fe"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"fo\"?",
    "options": [
      "フュ",
      "ウェ",
      "ウォ",
      "フォ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "フォ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"フォ\"?",
    "options": [
      "fa",
      "vu",
      "che",
      "fo"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "fo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the katakana for \"fyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "フェ",
      "フュ",
      "ファ",
      "ティ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "フュ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the romaji for \"フュ\"?",
    "options": [
      "di",
      "fyu",
      "tsi",
      "we"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "fyu"
  }
]

export default katakanaForeignSounds;